原创翻译  双语字幕
《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
所有知道超女秘密身份的人
Anyone who knows Supergirl's secret identity
都处于极大危险之中
is at incredible risk.
那我们要抹去超查部里所有
So, we wipe the minds of everyone at the DEO
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
知道我是超女的人的记忆
who knows I'm Supergirl.
我也必须清除记忆
I have to be mind-wiped, too.
-怎么了  -她改变了主意
- What happened? - She changed her mind.
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
打算留下孩子
She's gonna keep the baby.
你手上拿的是未经加工和稀释的试验血清
What you're holding is an experimental serum
它很可能会要了你的命
that will, in all likelihood, kill you.
校对     肉松  饿得慌
就是说有可能不会
That means it might not.
卡兹尼亚人入侵美国
A Kaznian invasion on American soil
就像一个孩子朝坦克扔石头
will be like a child throwing rocks at a tank.
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
-莱克斯有坦克  -红色之女
- Lex has a tank. - Red Daughter.
莱克斯·卢瑟联合了卡兹尼亚政府
Lex Luthor has allied with the Kaznian government,
后期     你是不是饿得慌
他们准备发起攻击
and they are going to attack.
我认为来提醒你更重要
I thought it was important to warn you.
总监     你是不是饿得慌
你做的没错
You did the right thing.
米德瓦尔  2007年
我有个想法
I... I've got an idea.
与其去上大学  不如不去上大学
Instead of going to college, how about not going to college?
卡拉  你没问题的
Kara, you'll be fine.
你只需要交一些新朋友
You just need to make some new friends.
或许你可以交一些懂节奏的朋友
Maybe you can make some friends with rhythm.
别人都不理解我
No one else gets me.
没有人能理解我
No one else can get me.
好吧  下一个拍手的部分要来了  别错过
Oh, okay. Next clapping part coming up. Don't miss it.
我没错过  我做的是爵士版本的
I didn't miss it. I was just doing like a jazz version.
好  准备好了吗
Okay, ready?
我做到了
I did it.
很好
Here we go.
卡拉
Kara!
你没事吧
You okay?
我做了个奇怪的梦  或者是回忆什么的
That was a weird dream or a memory or...
我不知道  是关于我妹妹的
I don't know. It was about, um, it was about my sister.
你那个领养的妹妹吗
Your sister who was adopted?
是啊
Yeah.
领养失败是件大事
An adoption falling through is a big deal.
这种事情不仅会引发情感问题
And stuff like that isn't just emotional.
也可能给你的大脑造成生理变化
It can make physiological changes to your brain
影响它内部的连接
and to the connections that it makes.
真奇怪
It's weird,
因为上一次我有这种感觉时
'cause the last time I felt like this,
我...
I was, uh...
我正在超查部接受调查
I was being questioned at the DEO.
是安全检查
It was a security sweep.
有些事情感觉不对劲  我觉得
Something just feels off, and I think...
不知为何  我觉得是和卡拉有关
I think it has to do with Kara somehow.
布莱尼  怎么了
Brainy, what's up?
我马上过去
I'm on my way.
华盛顿特区
天啊  这里是美国
Jeez, this is America.
你不能随意绑架记者
You can't just kidnap a reporter.
你也不能在涉及到国家安全的情况下
And you can't publish state secrets
公布国家机密
when it's a matter of national security.
我的编辑已经拿到了我手上的证据
My editor already has all my evidence.
我们销毁了凯特科的服务器
We scrubbed the CatCo servers.
你要把我关在这里多久
How long are you gonna keep me here?
直到总统告诉我们你不再是个麻烦
Until the President tells us you aren't a problem anymore.
你知道  我觉得不太能接受
You know, I don't really think that's gonna work for me.
蜘蛛
A spider!
你招惹错女孩了
You picked on the wrong girl.
超 女
第四季 第二十一集
洛克伍德部长进行哀悼的方式
Secretary Lockwood chose to cope with his grief
就是来了一场超能力侵袭
by going on a superpowered rampage.
他给自己注射了哈伦·艾尔吗
So he injected himself with Harun-El?
是的  他还拿走了所有库存
Yeah, and he took our entire stock.
然后还回来把这里捣毁了
And then he came back to trash the place to boot.
等一下  他就是关键
Wait. He's the key.
他一直以来就在我们眼前
And he's been in front of us the entire time.
-洛克伍德吗  -洛克伍德肯定和莱克斯有关系
- Lockwood? - Lockwood must be connected to Lex.
我们去卡兹尼亚找到了莱克斯的实验室
We went to Kaznia and we found Lex's lab.
他一直在对外星人做实验
He's been experimenting on aliens,
想要收集它们的能力
trying to harness their powers.
那里很多外星人
And a lot of these aliens
似乎是来自于超查部在沙漠的某个机构
seem to come from a DEO facility in the desert.
找到失踪的外星人  就能找到莱克斯
Find the missing aliens, find Lex.
但不管我们要采取什么措施  都要尽快
But whatever we do, we better do it fast.
-莱克斯正在计划入侵美国  -什么
- Lex is planning on invading America. - What?
你应该先说这件事
You should've led with that.
那下面这件事你肯定更感兴趣
Well, then you're gonna love this.
莱克斯克隆了超女
Lex has a clone of Supergirl.
-什么  -你应该先说这件事
- What? - You should've led with that.
超女接触哈伦·艾尔时产生了一个复制品
A copy was made when Supergirl touched the Harun-El.
她的名字叫红色之女
Her name's Red Daughter
莱克斯教导她去痛恨美国
and Lex has taught her to hate America.
这就解释了超女
This explains how Supergirl
被陷害袭击白宫的事情
was framed for the White House attack.
好吧  那我们现在怎么办
Right. So what do we do now?
我可以追捕那个反叛的氪星人
I can hunt a rogue Kryptonian.
我会找到她的  布莱尼  去吧
I will find her. Brainy, go.
去找荣恩  找到那些外星人
Get J'onn and find those aliens.
我会带梦想者一起去
I will bring Dreamer with.
我们会阻止莱克斯利用他们
We will stop Lex from using them
达成他的邪恶目的
for his nefarious purposes.
我还会告诉梦想者我爱上她了
And I will tell Dreamer that I am in love with her.
-太好了  -好的
- Great. - Okay.
-祝你好运  -谢谢
- Good luck. - Thank you.
不客气
Yeah.
我去和洛克伍德对质
I will rattle Lockwood
看他能否让我们找到莱克斯
and see if he leads us to Lex.
我有个计划
I have a plan.
我只需要跟超查部借一样东西
I just need to borrow something from the DEO.
-需要什么尽管拿  -好的
- Whatever you need. - Okay.
你有卡拉的消息吗
Hey, have you heard from Kara?
我打的电话她全都没接
She's not answering any of my calls.
她去通知总统我们的发现  卡拉没事的
She went to tell the President what we found. Kara's okay.
要知道  我本该杀了你
I'm supposed to kill you, you know.
我看出来了
I see that.
氪石让我虚弱
Kryptonite makes me soft.
你开枪的话我会流血
I bleed, you shoot me.
我去过卡兹尼亚了
I went to Kaznia.
我看到了你有我和我姐姐的照片
I saw those pictures you have of me, my sister.
-知己知彼  -拜托你不要这样做
- Know thy enemy. - Please don't do this.
我们是一样的  我们有相同的基因
We are the same. We have the same genes, the same--
看来我们到了故事里反派狡辩的部分
I see we've come to the part where the villain says
"你和我并没有那么不同"
"We are not so different, you and I."
我不是反派
I am not a villain.
"魔鬼也会引证《圣经》来为自己辩护"
"The devil can cite scripture for his purpose."
是莱克斯·卢瑟派你来的  对吗
Lex Luthor sent you here, right?
那么一旦你完成了他的命令
So once you've done his bidding,
他会怎样处置你
what's he gonna do to you?
他会杀你灭口
You're a loose end.
他告诉你的一切都是骗你的  他伤害他人
Everything he's told you, he's lying. He hurts people.
老天爷啊  去网上查查他
For God's sake, just look him up.
他做那些事是为了服务世界
He did those things in service to the world.
你是如此  受限
You are so limited.
你的生活本该意义重大
Your life could mean so much,
你却选择穿着啦啦队服飞来飞去
and yet you fly around in a cheerleader skirt.
他们是怎么做到的
How did they do it?
他们说了什么骗你信服
What did they say to make you believe?
看看窗外  你会看到
Look out the window and you will see
恐惧  种族主义  冲突
fear, racism, strife.
这个国家就像一头肥壮的小母牛
This country is a fatted heifer.
我来割开它的喉咙
I am here to cut its throat.
但首先
But first...
承认你错了
admit that you were wrong.
快说
Go on.
说你维护腐败势力
That you defend the corrupt.
美国梦就是骗子口中的灵药
The American dream is snake oil.
是谁将它卖给了你
Who sold it to you?
是你的艾丽克斯吗
Was it your Alex?
你说你想知己知彼
You know, for saying that you want to know your enemy,
可你完全不了解我
you don't know me at all.
例如  你正感受到的痛苦
For instance, that pain you're feeling,
你不过在过去几个月中有所接触
you've only felt it for the past couple of months.
而我
But me...
我已经应付氪石15年了
I've been dealing with Kryptonite for 15 years.
怎么回事
What happened?
别动
Just hold still.
就快好了  取出来了
Nearly got it. I got it.
只差一点  就能抓住他
I was so close. I had him.
我
I...
现在他们毁掉了我所有的证据
Now they've destroyed all my evidence,
我什么都没了
so I've got nothing.
洛克伍德逍遥法外
Lockwood walked,
人们认为超女是杀手
and people think Supergirl's an assassin,
总统联手了一个曾不止一次
and the President is working with a man
差点炸毁整个世界的人
who's almost blown up the world more than once.
别这样  别这么想
Come on. Don't do this.
我告诉自己
I told myself,
"笔杆更有力量
"Pen's mightier.
去做格兰特女士会做的事"
Let's do what Ms. Grant would do."
结果全都一败涂地
And it all fell apart.
你会找到出路的  你每次都能找到
Look, you'll find a way. You always do.
莱克斯知道我的身份
Lex knows who I am.
他想杀死我
He wants me dead.
那意味着艾丽克斯有危险  我
Which means Alex is in danger. I...
荣恩  我必须告诉她原因
J'onn, I have to tell her why.
她必须知道我是超女
She has to know I'm Supergirl. That's...
-她必须知道  -不行  卡拉
- She has to know. - You can't, Kara.
我抹去某人记忆的时候
Look, when I wipe somebody's mind,
会关闭神经通路
I close off neural pathways.
艾丽克斯的心智已经补上了失去的记忆
Alex's psyche has already compensated for the missing memories.
已经用墙隔离开了
They're walled off.
假如你告诉她实情
If you tell her the truth,
就像强行拆毁隔离墙
it's like you're taking a sledgehammer to that wall,
强迫两个现实融合  她可能会疯掉
forcing two realities together. She could go insane.
不能永远这样下去
This can't be forever.
肯定有办法的
There has-there has to be a way.
也许如果她
I mean, maybe if she...
自己发现
finds out on her own,
自己想起来了  也许吧
remembers on her own. Maybe.
那有可能吗
Is that possible?
我不知道
I don't know.
荣恩  我需要你帮忙
J'onn, I need your help.
卡拉  你受伤了
Kara. You're hurt.
之前是  但现在好了  艾丽克斯呢
I was, but I'm fine now. Where's Alex?
她正在调查超女的克隆人
She's looking into the Supergirl clone.
红色之女  莉娜全都告诉我们了
Red Daughter. Lena told us everything.
-她会害死自己的  -别去
- She's gonna get herself killed. - Don't do this.
我需要你帮忙找到那些外星人
Now I could use your help finding some aliens.
你怎么做到的
How did you manage this?
以营利为目的的监狱好处就是
Well, the nice thing about for-profit prisons
可以用钱买下来
is that you can buy them.
你把监狱买下来就为了帮我越狱吗
You bought a prison to get me out?
就这个周末
Just for the weekend,
这已经足够了
which is long enough for what I need.
这是小求真者
It's a baby Truth Seeker.
我需要真相
and I need the truth.
-你是说我不能骗人吗  -是的
- You mean, I can't lie? - Nope.
我的中学男朋友泰勒
My middle-school boyfriend, Taylor.
我给了他一万四  让他永远不要再理你了
I paid him $14,000 to never speak to you again.
我就知道
I knew it.
别担心  我不会问你是否爱我
Don't worry, I'm not gonna ask you if you love me.
我已经知道答案了
I already know the answer.
如果你有24小时  你会把哈伦·艾尔
If you had 24 hours, would you be able to extract the Harun-El
从本·洛克伍德的体内提取出来吗
from Ben Lockwood's system?
会的  为什么这么问
Yes. Why?
你觉得你做不到吗
You don't think you can do it?
莱克斯已经想出办法了  可我还没破解
Lex has figured out how, and I haven't cracked it yet.
但你们俩的思路很像
But your mind works like his.
虽然我很喜欢挑战
Well, as much as I love a challenge,
我们都知道这到底是为了谁
we both know who this is really for.
我为什么要帮吉米·奥尔森呢
And why would I ever do anything for Jimmy Olsen?
因为你的午餐里掺杂着奇异的神经毒素
Oh, because your lunch was laced with an exotic neurotoxin,
不  我是不会告诉你是哪一种的
and no, I'm not gonna tell you which one.
我有解药  我给你24小时的时间
I have the antidote,a and you have 24 hours.
我刚刚给了你一份礼物  好让你全力以赴
I've just given you the gift of focus.
既然这事如此重要
If this is so important,
你为什么不留下来帮我
why don't you stay and help me?
因为我要去找莱克斯
Because I've got to find Lex.
你不会正好知道他在哪吧
You don't happen to know where he is, do you?
当你发现你的孩子策划弑母时
When you find out your child was plotting matricide,
容易给母子关系蒙上一层阴影
it tends to cast a pall over the relationship.
他伤了你的心吗
Oh, did he hurt your feelings?
你就不能像个正常人一样用水邢来逼问我吗
Couldn't you just waterboard me like a normal person?
-你要去哪  -去和本·洛克伍德对质
- Where are you going? - To confront Ben Lockwood.
如果他把哈伦·艾尔带走了
If he's taken the Harun-El,
你应该等我提取完了再去
you should wait until I finish.
你在担心我吗
Oh, are you worried about me?
当然  我爱你
Of course. I love you.
好了  你让我说出来了
There. You have gotten me to say it.
局长
Director.
对不起  对不起  我只是来告诉你
I'm sorry! I'm sorry, I just came to tell you...
我知道你想找到红色之女
I know you're trying to find Red Daughter.
你不能来这里
You can't be here.
如果总统发现
If the President finds out...
他在和莱克斯合作
He's working with Lex.
-什么  -没错
- What? - Yeah.
你需要我
You need me,
尤其是在这个过程中  我们还要对抗
especially if we're gonna have to fight another me
另一个我
in the process.
你说他没空是什么意思
What do you mean he's unavailable?
我...  你可以告诉贝克总统
I... Well, you can tell President Baker
我有急事  本·洛克伍德...
that it's an emergency, and Ben Lockwood--
喂  喂
Hello? Hello...
喂
Hello?
本
Ben.
如果你是为了超能力酱料而来
If you've, uh, come for your super-sauce...
太迟了
Too late.
我知道你在和莱克斯合作
I know you're working with Lex.
我要知道他在哪
I need to know where he is.
你们这些人为什么一直说我认识他
Why do you people keep insisting that I know him?
因为你和奥蒂斯和默茜·格雷夫斯一起行动
'Cause you're running around with Otis and Mercy Graves
而他们是他的手下
and they're his henchpeople.
说吧  本杰明
Come on, Benjamin.
去年  你是个失业的历史学教授
Last year, you were an out-of-work history professor
现在是个有超能力的内阁成员
and now you're a cabinet member with superpowers.
你希望我相信这是个巧合吗
Do you expect me to believe that just happened?
是美国总统让我成为内阁成员的
The President of the United States made me a cabinet member.
总统听命于莱克斯
The President works for Lex.
你真的不知道
You really didn't know.
莱克斯耍了你
Lex played you.
他训练你  给了你武器和一份体面的工作
He gave you the training, the weapons, the fancy job,
现在你已经完成你的使命了
and now you've served your purpose.
你有没有想过这一切有点太过容易了
Did you never stop to think that this was all a little too easy?
容易
Oh, easy.
你认为这...
You think this was...
听清楚了
Okay, listen to me.
这是我的主意
This was my idea,
这是我的愿景  是我的心血
this was my vision, this was my work!
你曾经想拯救人类
You wanted to save the human race.
可是  你却将人类的未来交给了一个变态
Instead, you handed its future to a psychopath.
怎么样
So?
他根本不知道
He had no idea.
他看我的表情表明  他根本没有想到
The look he gave me, he hadn't even considered it.
所以他相信的一切都是谎言吗
So everything he believed in is a lie?
还有另外一件事
And there's another thing.
我觉得他的身体机能在退化
I think he's deteriorating
因为注射了哈伦·艾尔
because of the Harun-El.
-我不会那样吧  -不会
- That's not gonna happen to me, is it? - No.
本注射了未经测试的血清
Ben injected the untested serum.
不过等到明天  一切都无所谓了
And by tomorrow, it won't matter anyway.
我正在进行提取
I'm working on an extraction.
只有我这么觉得吗
Is it just me,
那个人似乎想寻找答案
or is that a man who needs answers?
也许这条线索并不是一条死胡同
Maybe this wasn't such a dead end after all.
这里是外星事务部最后一次搜查的地点
This is where the latest Alien Affairs raid took place.
抓走了三位外星人  我能感觉到他们的恐惧
Three aliens were taken. I can feel their fear.
-你认识这个东西吗  布莱尼  -什么
- Does this mean anything to you, Brainy? - What?
我不知道  妮娅在哪里
I... I don't know. Where's Nia?
她应该到了才对
She should be here by now.
我有一件很重要的事要跟她说
There's something very important I have to tell her.
好  但我们是不是应该先拯救世界
Okay, but shouldn't we try and save the world first?
不  我必须现在告诉她就是为了拯救世界
No! No, that's exactly why I have to tell her now.
我需要先把这件事解决
I need to get this out of my system
才有精力应付接下来的打斗和爆炸
before all the punching and exploding starts.
这个因果逻辑有点怪
Causality be damned.
只有告诉她我的感觉  我才能继续正常功能
If I tell her how I feel, normal function will resume.
爱情似乎不是这样的
I'm not sure that's how love works.
那是怎样的
How does it work?
什么是怎样的
How does what work?
墨西哥卷饼
Uh, tacos.
我刚才看到了一个梦境
I just had a vision.
那个钥匙链  一个外星女孩在骑独角兽
That keychain... An alien girl was riding that unicorn.
有一头狼在追她
She was being chased by a wolf.
狼代表着危险
Wolves are symbols of danger...
手机
Uh, phone.
好
Sure.
狼  脊索动物类  哺乳纲  食肉动物目
Wolf. Chordata, Mammalia, Carnivora...
不
Uh, no, no. Um...
爱尔兰语中狼的古语是"法尔"
The archaic word for wolf in Irish is faol...
法尔蓝货运公司  是一家附属公司的子公司...
Faolan Shipping maybe? They're a subsidiary of a subsidiary of...
隶属于莱克斯·卢瑟最爱的皮包公司
Lex Luthor's favorite shell company.
阿美特克
AmerTek.
法尔蓝货运公司
好了  到处都是私人安保摄像头
All right. Private security cameras everywhere,
还有抑制超能力的棍棒
power-dampening clubs.
他们在守卫一些重要的东西
They're guarding something important.
我有办法能让我们进去
I have an idea to get us in.
-我们玩一出伍奇神兵  -绝对不行
- We do a Wookiee Gambit. - Absolutely not.
伍奇什么
A Wookiee what?
你没看过《星球大战》吗
You haven't seen Star Wars?
你们已经为此
I believe I've been adequately
嘲笑过我好几次了  谢谢
shamed for that in the past, thank you.
基本就是荣恩变成守卫的样子
Basically, J'onn shapeshifts as a guard
假装押送我们进去
and pretends to bring us in as prisoners.
这是进去的最好办法了
It's the best way to get in.
为什么每个人都觉得被抓是最好的计划呢
Why does everyone always think getting captured is the best plan?
排好队
Stay in line!
布莱尼  跟我说一下几率
Brainy, tell me the odds.
我们假装被抓的话  有56.3%的几率
There is a 56.3% chance that faking our capture
会导致我们真的被抓
will lead to our actual capture.
看来伍奇不行
So, no Wookiee.
我会巡视一下周围
Look, I'll fly the perimeter,
看看能不能找到安全进去的方法
see if I can find a safe place to get us in.
你们留在这里  看好大门
You two stay here, watch the gate.
记录一下重要线索
Log anything important.
现在我们两个单独在一起了
Look, now that we have a moment alone,
我有话想跟你说
I have something to say to you.
过去的几个月里  我真的...
These past few months, I've really--
我的天哪
I can't believe it!
-怎么了  -是她
- What? - That's her.
我在梦境里看到的女孩
The girl from my vision.
那个钥匙链应该是她的
The keychain must have belonged to her.
布莱尼  她会遇到很糟糕的事情
Brainy, something terrible's gonna happen to her in there.
其实  56.3%对我们来说
You know what, 56.3 isn't that bad
并不算赖
by our standards.
我们去救她吧
Let's go get her.
用形象诱发器吗
Image inducer?
对
Yes.
必须得变成他们无法拒绝的人
I'll have to be someone they can't say no to.
是我
It is I, Secretary...
本杰明·洛克伍德部长
Secretary Benjamin Lockwood.
我已经抓到了外星罪犯梦想者
I have captured the alien outlaw Dreamer.
打开门
Open the gate
让我们进去
and allow us entry.
-成功了  -很显然
- It's working. - Obviously.
狗  我得跟你说多少次
Dog. How many times do I have to I tell you,
我们不能为了人类自己的邪恶目的
we cannot keep enslaving these animals
奴役这些动物
for our own, uh, nefarious purposes.
抱歉  先生  我们得检查
Sorry, sir, but we have to check.
我们被抓的可能性急剧升高
Our odds of being captured just went up.
照射阳光是什么感觉
How does it feel to, to burn sunlight?
温暖
Warm.
舒服
Fuzzy.
我的脚趾最先有感觉
I feel it in my toes first.
-有用吗  -好像有
- Is it working? - I think so.
她会像你一样转换太阳辐射
She's gotta convert solar radiation the same as you,
所以我用卫星专门给你扫射太阳辐射
so I am having the satellite scan for your solar signature
除去你去过的所有地方
and eliminate every place we know you've been.
剩下的肯定都是她
The rest must be her.
超女
Supergirl!
上校  你不是在华盛顿吗
Colonel, I thought you were in Washington.
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
竟然把敌人带到超查部来
You brought an enemy combatant into the DEO?
不 她在这是因为真正的敌人在外面
No, she's here because the real enemies are on the way.
我们猜对了
We were right.
我的复制版袭击了白宫
A copy of me attacked the White House.
或者说一个克隆的我
A clone, more or less.
总统也知情
The President knew, too.
贝克总统一直在帮莱克斯·卢瑟
Baker's been working for Lex Luthor.
现在卢瑟计划袭击美国
And now Luthor is planning on attacking the US.
所以我们就必须联手对抗敌人
Then, I guess that's why we should work together on this.
-布莱尼  -你们要把她带到哪去
- Brainy! - Hey, where are you taking her?
放开她
Let her go!
她在哪
Where is she?
你要是敢伤害她
If you hurt her...
你就怎样
You'll what?
这里所有人
Everyone else in here,
都有强大的超能力
they've got these crazy powers.
而你  我看来
You, far as I can tell,
只是皮肤蓝而已
are blue.
不过那个女孩
The girl, on the other hand...
拜托 拜托
Please, please...
你怎么折磨我都行  但别伤害她
Do whatever you want with me, but do not hurt her.
别担心  她是下一个
Don't worry, she's next.
你不许伤害她
You will not hurt her!
怎么有人会伤害她
Why would anyone hurt her...
搞定了
He's done.
下一个  兄弟们
On to the other one, boys.
不要  不要
No. No!
不要  不行  不行
No! No, you can't! You can't!
小盒子  盒子
Little boxes. Boxes...
盒子最终都会打开
Eventually boxes get opened.
这好像是个故事
There's a story about that, right?
是希腊故事吗
It's Greek?
你们太不开化了
You're just primitives.
我这么努力回到这里来
And I have worked so hard to get back here.
你们忘了穿越时间的同时也穿越了空间
You people forget that time travel is also space travel too.
地球每小时移动67000英里
You see, Earth is moving at 67,000 miles per hour.
出现在不同的时间  不同的地点
And at different times, it's in different places,
所以你必须准确计算  否则就会流落太空
so you got to do the math or else you end up in space.
而准确计算没那么简单
And the math is not easy!
我是想说  我是想说  我是想说
My point is... My point is, my point is,
我来自未来
I'm from the future.
你们好像把他弄疯了
I think you knocked the dots off his dice.
我要告诉你们
What I'm trying to tell
我们这一人种有祖先的记忆
you is that my species has ancestral memory.
我们的祖先
And my ancestors,
都是大恶人
very bad people.
他们是掠夺者  征服者
They were collectors, conquerors...
我什么都记得
I remember everything!
不要想
Don't want...
总之  你们重启了我
In short, you rebooted me.
给我匹配了更多
Aligned me with my more...
残酷的祖先
emotionless ancestors.
这错误是致命的
And that was a calamitous mistake.
住手
Stop!
怎么回事
What happened?
我自由了
I'm free.
红色之女看样子很忙
Well, Red Daughter's been busy.
克莱莫行动  还记得吗
Project Claymore. You remember it?
我记得每个被我炸掉的秘密政府宇宙激光器
I remember every secret government space laser I've blown up.
我很不满他们隐瞒我  便去华府调查
I hated that they hid it from me, so I went to DC to ask around.
克莱莫的光束由不明能源供能
The beam from Claymore was powered by an unknown energy source.
六个工程师参与研发
There were six engineers involved in R and D,
于是我去追踪他们
and when I tried to track them down,
结果发现他们
I found out they all got put
都在过去两周被铁铲攻击致死
to bed with a shovel in the last two weeks...
分别在这些地点
in these locations.
卢瑟想获取克莱莫的科技
Luthor's trying to get a hold of Claymore technology.
我们得找到并阻止他
We need to find him and stop him from getting it,
但现在首要任务是找到红色之女
but right now, our priority is finding Red Daughter.
对这些地点作三角测量  能找出地址吗
So if we triangulate these hits, can we get an address?
这些都在纳欣诺市中心
These are all downtown National City.
在一天的不同时间
Different times of the day and night.
你觉得她就住在这吗
Do you think she's living here?
纳欣诺市  雪松路  1114号
我们没法派后援
We won't be able to send back-up.
因为没有我们能信任的人
Not without knowing who we can trust.
没事  我会自己找到她
It's fine. I'll find her alone.
慢着  等一下
Hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait a minute.
我们会找到她的  我也要去
We'll find her. I'm coming too.
不  太危险了
No, it's too dangerous.
你在这里更安全  局长
You'll be safer here, Director.
你为什么这么奇怪  我们在一起抓她啊
Why are you acting so weird? We're hunting her together.
我只需要你相信我
I just need you to trust me.
我一个人去
I'm going alone.
纳欣诺市  雪松路  1114号
拉奥
Oh, Rao.
你在跟踪我
You're stalking me.
他们在吸取外星能量
They're draining alien power
转化成动能去制作
and converting it to kinetic energy for use in
类似克莱莫粒子武器的东西
what looks like a version of the Claymore particle weapon.
但屋里好像
Yet there does not appear
没有任何提取设备
to be any extraction equipment on premises.
我发现了一个物质传送门
I did find a Transmatter Portal.
他们一定在把外星人逃犯转移到另一个地方
Then they must be moving the alien prisoners to a second location
去吸取能量了
to drain their power.
我们必须找到并摧毁它
We must find and disable it.
是的  布莱尼  那梦想者呢
Yeah, sure. But, Brainy, what about Dreamer?
对  她可能会有用
Yes. She could be useful.
我想我知道她被带去哪里了
I believe I know where they took her.
你...
Hey, are you...
你还好吗
Are you feeling okay?
我一点也没觉得痛
I am not experiencing any pain.
想不到你今天会因吃枪子而死吧
Didn't think you'd die today. Dine on bullets.
这不是自由部长吗
Oh! If it isn't Secretary Liberty.
大本  我真为你骄傲
Big Ben! Proud of you, buddy.
怎么了
What's up?
在这忙着呢  避避风头
Kind of busy here, lying low,
等待下一步计划
waiting on the next step of the plan.
这样啊
Yeah.
在这个旧藏身处
In the old safehouse.
是啊  莱克斯不想让我用  但是...
Yeah. Lex didn't want me to use it, but...
我得用  我很怀旧
I had to. I'm sentimental, you know?
我妹妹  她喜欢这个地方
My sister, she loved this spot.
你妹妹...
Your sister...
你和你妹妹接近我的时候
When you and your sister approached me...
你在为莱克斯工作吗
were you working for Lex then?
当然了
Of course.
卢瑟想让我成为代表
Luthor wanted me to become Agent--
没人叫你戴面具
Hey! Nobody told you to wear the mask.
那都是你的主意
That was all you.
但其他的确实是
But the rest of it, yeah.
我没发现有问题
Well, I don't see the problem, man.
这是三赢
It's a win-win-win.
双赢
Win-win.
我失去了一切
I lost everything.
不  你有权力  我有钱  莱克斯有更多钱
No. You get power, I get money, Lex gets more money.
奥蒂斯  你是在说  发生的这一切
Otis, so you're saying that everything that's happened, all of this,
都是为了钱吗
you're telling me that it's all about money?
还有统治世界
And world domination.
这是他的追求
It's kind of his thing.
我懂了  不
I get it. No.
超级反派  对  我懂了
Supervillain, right. I get it.
奥蒂斯  他在计划什么
Otis, what's he planning?
卡兹尼亚的欢乐时光  纸老虎
Fun time in Kaznia. Paper tigers, man.
纸老虎
Paper tigers.
是"纸老虎"
It's "Paper tigers."
是个阴谋行动
It's a false flag operation.
莱克斯让卡兹尼亚入侵美国  背叛他们
Lex convinces Kaznia to invade the US, betrays them--
然后他自己去阻止
And then he stops it himself.
莱克斯成了他一直自以为的英雄
Lex becomes the hero he always thought he was.
你知道规矩  既然我告诉你了
You know the rules, now that I told ya...
我就要杀了你
I gotta kill you.
有头有尾  毕竟也是我挑选了你
Kind of fits. Seeing as I'm the one who picked you.
无聊的老本·洛克伍德
Boring old Ben Lockwood.
奥蒂斯  名字是...
Otis, the, uh... The name...
是自由
...is Liberty.
不不  洛克伍德  我们需要他来找到莱克斯
No, no, no, no, Lockwood. We need him to find Lex.
詹姆斯
James!
你死定了
Now you're dead.
真残忍  兄弟
Harsh, bro.
游戏结束
Game over.
詹姆斯  詹姆斯  我会治好你
James? James, I'm gonna fix this.
-布莱尼  -五号
- Brainy. - The fifth.
给我四秒钟帮你松绑
Give me four seconds to release your bindings.
可你是怎么逃出来的
But how did you escape?
你的手铐打开了  再给我四秒钟
Your hands are free. Give me four more seconds.
你现在可以入侵网络吗
You can hack the network now?
可以
Yes.
我做的事情更专精
I am much more focused.
那你可以释放所有被抓的外星人
Then you can free all the captive aliens.
其实我有件事情得告诉你
Actually, there's something I have to tell you.
布莱尼
Brainy...
我不准备放你走
I'm not going to release you.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你得穿过传送门
You have to go through the portal.
什么
What?
你一到了另一边  就进行星体投射
Once you're on the other side, astral project.
告知我位置
Inform me of the location
我们会解救营地并击败卢瑟
and we'll liberate the camp and foil Luthor.
布莱尼  你不能这么做
Brainy, you can't do this.
我以为你会高兴
I thought you would be happy.
毕竟这本身就是你的主意
After all, this was your idea in the first place.
布莱尼  布莱尼  布莱尼
Brainy. Brainy. Brainy!
布莱尼
Brainy!
布莱尼  梦想者在哪里
Brainy, where's Dreamer?
我把她留在里面了
I left her behind.
当她到了下一个地点
She'll send us an astral projection
她会进行星体投射
when she arrives at the next location.
我们不能留她一个人
We are not leaving her alone.
你没错
You're right.
如果你和她一起过去  我们胜算更大
We double our odds if you're taken through the gate with her.
布莱尼
Brainy.
你会在两分钟十四秒之后恢复行动能力
You will regain your ability to move in two minutes, 14 seconds.
正好够你被抓
Just enough time for you to be captured.
如果你们俩都失败了
And if you both fail,
我会想出别的办法
well, then I'll just think of something else.
我一向如此
I always do.
米凯尔
Mikhail.
你好
Hey.
艾丽克斯  你在这里干什么
Alex, what are you doing here?
我告诉过你  你不能把我留在里面
I told you, you're not leaving me behind.
为什么这个地方
Why does this place
看着这么像我妹妹的公寓
look so much like my sister's apartment?
艾丽克斯
Alex...
我知道
I know...
这特别奇怪
This is all very strange.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我从这里可以看到卡拉的阁楼
I can see Kara's loft from here.
就好像她在跟踪卡拉
It's like she's stalking her.
但是卡拉会没事的
But Kara's gonna be okay.
你不用担心她
You don't have to worry about her.
除非你有姐妹  要不然你不会
Unless you have a sister you don't understand...
明白这种感觉
this feeling.
我有过一个姐妹
I had one.
那你肯定知道
Well, then you know it--
这就像一块心头肉
It's like a piece of my heart is out there
独自在外四处游荡
and it's just wandering around in the world,
而我却没能力保护她
and it's on its own and I can't protect it.
我保护不了她
I can't protect her.
不管怎样
And no matter what, I mean,
危险总会存在
there's always gonna be danger.
但我无法一直保护她
But I can't always be there for her,
这实在是  这不是
and this is... This is not...
对不起  我
I'm sorry. I, uh...
妈  你好  一切都好吗
Mom, hey, um, is everything all right?
很好  亲爱的  只想让你知道
Oh, yes, honey. Just wanted to let you know
卡拉到这里了
that Kara just got here.
很好  她还好妈
Oh, good. Is she okay?
是的  她让我打电话给你
Oh, yeah. She asked me to call you
为了告诉你她没事
just to make sure you knew she was safe.
-红色之女在那里  -什么
- Red Daughter is there. - What?
伊莉莎  她有危险
Eliza, uh... She's in danger.
告诉她离开那里
Tell her to get out!
妈  你还在吗
Mom, are you still there?
妈
Mom?
伊莉莎
Eliza?
卡拉
Kara...
别伤害她  拜托了
Don't hurt her, please.
我来这里几个小时了
I've been here for hours.
你有这些
You have all these...
东西
things.
你以为这些会让你变得完整
You think they will make you whole?
我什么都没有
I had none of it.
-你依旧能拥有这些  -我不想要这些
- You can still have it. - I don't want it.
那你为什么在城市里有间公寓
Then why do you have an apartment in the city?
我知道你对莱克斯有所顾忌
I know you have doubts about Lex--
他的名字是艾丽克斯
His name is Alex!
好的  好的  别激动
Okay, okay, easy.
你保护他人
You protect individuals.
那是懦弱的表现
That is weakness.
我为集体服务
I serve the collective.
那米凯尔怎么回事
What about Mikhail?
我知道他对你很重要
I know he's important to you.
你提起米凯尔真是有意思
Interesting that you should bring Mikhail up.
美国人杀了他
Americans killed him.
妈  卡拉  请接电话
Mom, Kara, please pick up.
我不知道出了什么事
I don't know what's wrong.
超女去你们那里了  我也在路上
Supergirl's headed to you and I'm on my way as well.
卢瑟会背叛卡兹尼亚
Luthor will betray Kaznia.
也会背叛你的
And he will betray you.
-不  他为  -自己而战
- No, he fights for-- - Himself!
他一直都这样
That's all he's ever done.
并非所有人都像你一样自私
Not everyone is as selfish as you.
对万物抱有希望  帮扶和同情之心
Hope, help, and compassion for all.
那才是我的信念
That's what I stand for.
等我解决了你  你的信念就不存在了
You will not be able to stand at all when I am done with you.
你觉得结果会如何
How do you think this ends?
我们有相同的能力
We have the same powers.
不完全是
Not exactly.
我进化了
I am evolved.
屈服吧
Submit.
我只要活着就不会屈服
Not while I'm still breathing.
敬丹弗斯姐妹
Here's to the Danvers sisters.
这一次让我来救你
Let me save you this time.
卡拉
Kara.
不
No.
No!
不  不  不
No No No No
不  你现在不能走
No. You can't go now.
所有事  我都记起来了
I remember... everything.
卡拉  我们在这  我们都在这
Kara, we're here, we're here. We're here together.
我了解你
And I know you.
我比任何人都了解你
I know you better than anybody knows you.
我知道你不会放弃
And I know that you don't quit.
所以你现在不能走
So you can't go now!
卡拉  你不能走
Kara, you can't go!
不  不
No, no!
艾丽克斯
Alex.
没事的  妈妈  她没事的
It's okay. Mom, she's... She's okay.
她会没事的  只是天太黑了
She's gonna be fine. It's just dark,
没有阳光  但是
so there's no sunlight, but there's...
万物都有阳光
There's sunlight in everything.
草里有阳光
There's sunlight in the grass.
卡拉  吸收它
So, Kara, just take it.
吸收这些草
Take the grass!
求你了
Please.
卡拉  别
Kara, no.
别离开我
Please don't leave me.
艾丽克斯  她在做了
Alex, she's doing it.
她在吸收阳光
She's pulling the sunlight.
我在这  我在这
I'm here. I'm here.
我非常想你
I've missed you so much.
我真的很想你
I really missed you.
-莉莉安  准备好了吗  -好了
- Lillian. Is it ready? - Yes.
这边  带他过来
Here. Bring him here.
没事的
It's okay.
这里
Here.
-开始提取  -不
- Starting extraction. - No!
我们不知道会发生什么  我需要我的力量
We don't know what's coming. I need my strength.
-你不稳定  -那就让我稳定
- You're unstable. - Then stabilize me.
我们束手无策
We don't know how.
事实上  再来一剂哈伦·艾尔就可以
Actually, another dose of the Harun-El would do it.
我们不知道那会对他有什么影响
We don't know what that would do to him.
我研究了一整天  亲爱的  掌握了一些信息
I've been studying it all day, dear. I've learned things.
我能说谎吗
Would I lie?
注射吧
Do it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不用谢  吉米
You're welcome, Jimmy.
喝了这个
Drink this.
说吧  你不会给我下毒
Oh, come now. You didn't really poison me.
你该喝了这个
You should drink it.
哈雷上校
Colonel Haley.
我知道和克莱莫的关联了
I found the connection with Claymore.
这是一个原型
It was a prototype.
他们制作了一个缩小版
They made a compact version.
有多小
How compact?
小到可以放入莱克斯奥服
Small enough for Lexosuit.
他用了吗
Has he used it?
入侵我们国家的
...an invasion of our country...
把电视声音开大
Turn on the television.
和危险的国家卡兹尼亚
...and the dangerous rogue state of Kasnia,
不是别人  正在超女
none other than Supergirl.
这些影像是刚拍摄到的
These images captured moments ago
证明了这个人单枪匹马
prove that one man single-handedly
挫败了侵略者  杀死了恐怖分子  超女
thwarted the invaders and kill the terrorist, Supergirl.
这个人就是莱克斯·卢瑟
That man is Lex Luthor.
卢瑟先生
Mr. Luthor,
一个懂得感恩的国家谢谢你
a grateful nation thanks you.
怎么会这样
How did this happen?